Oh, so it's like The View.
Sheldon, The View is a daytime
talk show hosted by women.
Oh, I'm aware.
It features Whoopi Goldberg.
She played Guinan on
Star Trek: Next Gen.
Penny, Next Gen
refers to Star Trek...
(Penny:)Shut up.
(Raj:)I would like to
propose a salon topic.
(Amy:)Ooh, please do, Rajesh.
The lead in The Hunger
Games is a woman.
(Raj:)Marvel has made
"Tor" a female.
(Penny:)Wait, who's Tor?
(Raj:)You know, Tor,
the God of "Tunder."
(Raj:)As I was saying,
is this a sign
(Raj:)that our society is
approaching gender equality?
(Howard:)Certainly a lot more women
are reading comic books now.
(Stuart:)It's true.
(Stuart:)At the store, I had to put
a seat on the toilet.
(Amy:)We won't know
if there's equality
(Amy:)until female Thor has a baby
(Amy:)and the Avengers are cool with
her pumping breast milk at work.